

# **MUSTAFA**

Software Developer

## ABOUT ME

A dedicated, responsible, and committed Computer Scientist, having a get-it-done product and project spirit, with 2+ years of Professional experience designing, implementing, deploying back-end Web, Mobile, and Desktop applications using a variety of Programming languages

#### CONTACT

+92 336 1878341

mustafatahirhussein@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/mustafatahirhussein

# PORTFOLIO

https://github.com/mustafatahirhussein https://www.behance.net/mustafatahirhussein https://play.google.com/store/apps/developer?id= UniqueDeveloper365

# PERSONAL SKILLS

Self-Motivated and independent. Problem Solving Skills Ability to perform multi-tasks

## INTERESTS

Programming, recording videos, learning new things, Article writing etc.

# **EDUCATION**

## BACHELORS (B.S) IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

IQRA University, Karachi 2016 - 2019

#### PRE-ENGINEERING

Pakistan Shipowners' Government College 2013 - 2015

#### **MATRICULATION**

St. Lawrence's Boys' School 2004 - 2013

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## App Developer - Flutter

Parazelsus Pakistan Pvt Ltd

08/2021 - Ongoing

- Enhanced features of the existing Parazelsus App.
- Ensured best possible solution to Customers.
- Parazelsus Web Support (Flutter Web) for getting Feedbacks.
- State Management Provider.

#### Software Developer - Flutter

Chimp Advertising 08/2020 - 08/2021

- Worked with a team of 5 members and provided end-to-end
- Lead Junior Flutter interns for different Projects.
- Deployed Applications to Playstore & Appstore.
- Used State Management tactics.

#### Flutter Developer

Solution Hub 12/2019 - 06/2020

- Worked with a team of 3 members and provided Solutions.
- Designed & developed applications using Flutter & Native codes.

#### .Net Intern

Codegasm UK 09/2019 - 11/2019

Designed & developed a Point-of-Sale System.

#### Web Intern

Interns Pakistan 02/2019 - 04/2019

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

#### Tools & IDE

NetBeans, MS Visual Studio, Visual Code, Sublime, Dreamweaver, Smart Git, IntelliJ IDEA, Dev C++, Android Studio, DartPad, Postman, JIRA.

## Database Management

SQL Server 2014, MySQL, SQLite, SqfLite, Hive, Drift.

#### Programming Languages

Dart, Android, Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Python, C++, C#.

## **Cloud-Based Technologies**

GitHub, Google Sheets